reqall.com 2013-12-25

# 

**Introduction**  
We respect your privacy. When you register with us and use our website and related services, you consent to our use of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, and any such updates will be effective as of the date we post the updated Privacy Policy on our website. 

We include in this Privacy Policy the following information: 

  * What personally identifiable information we collect, and how and when we collect it 
  * How long we keep the information 
  * How we use the information 
  * Whether we disclose the information we collect to third parties 
  * The options you have to control the use of the information 
  * Our use of your IP address 
  * How we use “cookies” 
  * Linking to third party websites 
  * What security measures we use to protect the information we collect 
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy 
  * How to contact us if you have any questions 

**Personally Identifiable Information We Collect and How We Collect It**  
We collect certain personally identifiable information from you in order to make your experience with our services as satisfactory as possible. In order to use our services, you must register, and we ask you to provide certain personally identifiable information at that point. You may also include personally identifiable information in the data you post in the course of using our services. 

When you register for one of our services, we collect the following information to establish your account: your name, email address, phone number and password. When you register for a reQall Pro account, we also collect your credit card number, card type, verification code, billing address, and expiration date. If you connect any reQall service to any 3rd party services, such as Gmail, Google Calendar, Facebook or Twitter, we will collect your account information for those services. 

In the process of using our services, you will probably submit information by voice or text, such as tasks, ideas, meetings notes, birthdays and the like. Some of these messages or reminders may contain information that could identify you. You may also assign locations to your items and provide the geo-coordinates of those locations. You may also set up reQall to remember the geo-coordinates of where you create items. reQall has no control over the content of these messages or reminders, who you decide to share them with, or to whom you give access to your login information. 

If you use reQall Action, we securely transmit your email content to our reQall Action servers with industry-standard SSL encryption. The server identifies the actionable phrases and transmits these securely back to your browser. Your email is not stored on our servers or communicated to anyone else. If you give us feedback about reQall Action suggestions, we will securely store that information to improve how reQall Action provides future suggestions. 

We also collect personally identifiable information that you give us when you respond to communications from us. 

**How Long Do We Keep Your Personally Identifiable Information?**  
We keep the personally identifiable information that you submit to us when you register as long as your account with us remains active. 

At any time, you may terminate your account, or ask us to do that for you. When your account is terminated, all of the personally identifiable information that we collected about you during the registration process is automatically deleted from our on-line servers. However, we may continue to have your information in our backup databases indefinitely. 

**How We Use the Information**  
The information we collect from you at time of registration is used to identify your account so that data you enter while using the service goes into your account and not some other user’s account. We also use your email address to communicate with you when you have questions or to inform you about our services. If you have elected to use our Pro service beyond the end of the free trial, we will pass your name, credit card number, security code, billing address, and expiration code on to the appropriate merchant vendor who will use it to charge your card. We use your account information for 3rd party services to connect your reQall services to those services. If you give us feedback about reQall Action suggestions, we will use that information to improve how reQall Action provides future suggestions. 

The information you submit while using our services can be entered either by voice or by text. We convert voice messages to text using automated speech recognition technology.

If you ask us for help in using our services, we may need to look at information you have submitted in order to provide appropriate support. We limit who can look at this information to a small number of employees. Those employees are the ones most qualified to assist you with your support needs, and they are all obligated to respect and safeguard the confidential information of our users. 

We use certain non-personally identifiable information we receive from you to increase the functionality and user-friendliness of our website, products and services and to better tailor them to your needs. We also use this information to monitor onsite activity in the aggregate. For example, we may monitor how long the average user spends on our site or which pages or features get the most attention. 

**Disclosure to Third Parties**  
Except as stated herein, we never rent, sell, trade or give away your personally identifiable information to third parties. We do not publicly disseminate the personally identifiable information that you voluntarily submit to your account (by email, phone or other telecommunications device). We are not responsible for your actions that result in such information becoming publicly disseminated. 

We may share certain information from you with contractors and vendors to the extent necessary to maintain and successfully provide our services. For example, we may give audio recordings that you have entered into our system to contractors who help us do audio transcription. The data we share in this manner cannot be associated with any user’s personally identifiable information, such as a particular account name, email address or phone number. However, some contractors and vendors, such as those providing voice to text transcription, would have access to any personally identifiable information that you put into the messages that you submit to our system. All such contractors and vendors are required to sign confidentiality agreements. 

As is standard in the industry, we use third-party vendors to distribute newsletters and email announcements. We require those vendors to also maintain the confidentiality of your information, such as your email address. 

To the extent required by law, we may disclose personally identifiable information to government authorities, or to third parties pursuant to a subpoena or other legal process, and we may also use or disclose your information as permitted by law to protect our rights or the rights of our other users. 

As our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. It is also conceivable that reQall could be acquired by another company. In the event that we sell some or all of our assets, or we are acquired by another company, information about you may be among the transferred assets. 

**Options to View, Update, Correct and Control the Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information**  
You can view all of the personally identifiable information you submitted to us when you established your account and also the messages you have submitted when using our services (except those that you have deleted). You may edit that information to update or correct it. You may also delete your account and all the personally identifiable information that you submitted when you registered with us. 

**Our Use of Your IP Address**  
An Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We will use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address also may be used to gather broad demographic information that is not personally identifiable. 

**How We Use “Cookies”**  
A “cookie” is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites. We use cookies to collect, store and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the services we provide. We also use cookies to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your personally identifiable information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit other websites you may be required to accept cookies. Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. 

**Links to Third Party Websites**  
Our website, as well as the information we transmit to the mobile device portion of our services, contains hyperlinks and pointers to Internet sites maintained by third parties. These links are provided for your reference only. We do not control, operate or endorse in any respect information, products or services on such third-party sites and are not responsible for their content. Many third-party sites have their own privacy policies that differ from ours. This Privacy Policy only covers our website and does not cover any other site. While we make every effort to keep your information secure, we do not control the policies of other websites. 

**Security**  
reQall uses a number of measures to maintain the security of your personally identifiable information. The personal information we collect is stored within databases that we control directly or through our service providers. reQall’s servers and its hosted databases are located in a secure hosting facility. We use firewalls and VPN connections to prevent access to the information we store by non-authorized individuals. Our security measures are consistent with industry standards to protect your information. However, while we institute physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information, and we regularly review our security standards and procedures to protect against unauthorized access to personal information, we cannot guarantee absolute security due to the inherent risks associated with storing and transmitting information electronically, wirelessly, or otherwise over the Internet or other telecommunications methods. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
As technology and our services evolve, we may need to update our Privacy Policy periodically. If we do so, we will revise the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. By continuing to use our services after we post any such update, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified. 

**How to Contact Us**  
Feel free to send us any questions or comments you may have via email to [support@reqall.com](mailto:support@reqall.com).

Last Updated: November 1, 2010
